Zhang Chenxi
Teacher Zhang
Why is he everywhere?
I didn't expect the protagonist's aura to be so strong.
It's like everyone is fighting over me.
Floating again.
The feeling you give me until now
is still like yesterday.
Just a
perfect boy.
High praise.
Hello.
I see your expression, do you have an appointment?
I'm here
waiting for you.
The person I chose happened to choose me too.
What's going on today, it's all words.
I think it's just
you also need to be firmly chosen.
Sorry.
Are you confused?
I'm so angry.
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) is really brave, to be honest.
These past few days, I am
I want to understand Liang Tian.
But now I'm very confused.
I don't really know
how to face you in the future.
I feel like a backup.
No.
I'm not a brave person.
But I tried.
Although I'm happy he stayed,
how did I become a part of this game?
Casual encounters
This show is brought to you by the popular
Soul APP
exclusively sponsored broadcast
Global beauty and health products
on the Watsons mini program
Thanks to the beauty of health and the health of beauty
jointly sponsored by Watsons
Welcome everyone
What is happening here
is a Tencent Video original
mature love observation reality show
"Half-Mature Lovers" Season 4
Hello everyone, I am Zhang Chunye
Let's welcome
all our friends in the observation room
Welcome Teacher Du
Welcome Xu Yiyang
Welcome Tang Yixin
Welcome Zhu Xudan
And Lu Hu
Welcome everyone
Last time we saw
the invitation segment
three pairs forming one-on-one combinations
Let's watch together
You are my only one
Hello
"Left-behind children"
Who is it? That's so hurtful.
Hello
I just checked if you were awake.
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
Do you want to eat?
I already ate.
Your hair today is so
punk, isn't it?
Will this take a long time?
Yes
You look pretty good.
I noticed you.
Your hair is always slightly off-center.
Is that so?
Yes.
It should be a little off-center.
Just making small talk.
Have you eaten already?
You've started drawing, right?
Yes, I went.
Alright, go ahead.
Actually, I feel quite awkward.
Because in a short period of time,
I don't know how to face it
Including when I chat with him
I also say
I said I don't really know in the future
how to face you
But he might
be more proactive in breaking
be more proactive in breaking this deadlock
It's a bit awkward now
His body proportions are really good.
Why are you waiting outside?
Your coat looks really nice.
Today, both of us are wearing grey.
It's pretty good.
The weather is also pretty good today.
Perfect for a date.
Really nice.
Let's just be together.
From last night until now,
today has been my happiest day.
First of all,
Wowo (Ren Jiabi) knocked on my door.
She is not usually this proactive.
But after she knocked,
it felt like a mutual effort.
When we realized that both of us
had taken the first step forward,
I would then put in more effort
to take the remaining ninety-nine steps towards her.
Run towards her with all my might.
Getting ready to go downstairs.
Right away.
Just one last step.
Use this L'Oréal hair oil.
Just one or two pumps.
Deeply nourishes hair while reducing frizz
Makes my hair so smooth it shines
Smells good
Right?
Let's go
That place is up to you
Goodbye
Are you ready?
Let's go
So happy
Really good
When I finally made the choice
Still
I chose based on my own heart, Zheng Weiying
Because relatively speaking, the two of us
Have spent quite a lot of time together
All along
There really is a kind of
This particularly relaxed feeling
Feeling better?
My throat hurts a bit today
It's inflamed
Put it here
Then we're leaving
Goodbye
Taller than me
I'm really looking forward to
continuing to date her
we can find more
similarities between us
or differences
if there's any spark
So pitiful
Today, couples are leaving one by one
It feels like the room
is getting emptier
feels a bit abandoned in the small house
The remaining Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
and Brother Luo (Luo Junfan)
I feel very lonely
I thought I would be the only one at home
Luckily, they are here with me
The sunlight is a bit glaring, right?
Indoor surfing is suitable.
Choosing surfing for a date is quite brave.
I want to choose the full-body one.
Then this blue one.
Let's choose the same color.
Blue.
Okay.
I got you a towel.
Thank you.
You are very considerate.
You are quite professional in sports.
I wouldn't remember these things.
Have you two surfed before?
No.
I tried it once a long time ago.
Alright, I'll go in and try it first.
I can finally be happy
and go on a date with someone I want to
without any pressure
and enjoy a date
He is cheering himself up
His expression is so genuine
You
Hello
The limbs are extremely long
Stop teasing me
I'll guide you through a comprehensive move
This move is called the Greatest Stretch
Do you know why it's called
the Greatest Stretch?
No, I don't.
Because the person who invented it is the greatest.
Did he invent it himself?
First, step out with one of your legs.
Make a lunge.
Okay.
Yes, go as low as possible.
Then, touch the ground with the elbow on this side.
Alright.
Yes, very good.
The coach is getting serious again.
Coach, am I doing it right?
Very good.
Then, as you...
slowly raise your arm...
Very good, you...
Okay
Teacher, you just hit my sore spot
So this can warm up quickly
I was worried before
In winter
it would be cold
doing this activity
might catch a cold
The worry is unnecessary
I can see that you are really in good shape
I also sweat a lot
Okay, then we will
increase the difficulty
Is this okay?
Yes
It’s not okay either
Hello
How was your warm-up?
We sweated
Very thoroughly
Yes
Great
Then let's start surfing
Okay
Go for it
Surf over here
So scary
This is very difficult
Help
Coach, we can't stand on this wave, right?
No, you can
Everyone can balance on their first try
I'll show you
Don't be nervous
I'll fall first to show you
You go first
I really am, this
Okay, at this position
Yes
First, place your back foot properly
Then move your front foot back a bit
This foot, okay, almost
Let it touch the wall
Then stand up, stand straight
Stand again, stand straight
Very good
You stood up
He can't either
He got washed down
So I said they chose surfing for this date
So brave
Because it will be very embarrassing
The back is getting shallower
But the wave is so big, he can't stand
No
Challenge it
Come
Move the board forward
Stand on one side
Okay
I don't dare
Okay, come, stand straight
Sit up
Because he is actually very good at sports
Although I'm not good at it
But I also like it
So we chose a project
But we actually missed one thing
I'm really terrified of water
She is also afraid of water
I'm really scared
So scared
Cried
I think so
Let's go from this side
Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
Let's go down from there
From that side
I really heard such a loud sound of water
I was already very scared and panicked
Look, stand inside first
Then look, I walk here
Can you stand here?
I can't stand over there right now
Pull me over
I really can't get over
It's okay, just pull me
The force is too strong
It's okay, take it slow
I'm protecting you
The water is too deep.
Yes, you need to sit for a while.
Here.
Put this on.
Aren't you going to use it? Wipe yourself off.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Sit for a while.
Watch me fall a few more times and you'll be fine.
The more I watch, the more scared I get.
He can't do it either.
It really feels difficult.
Give me a little more time.
Okay
Stop right there
You still have talent
talented
This sport definitely requires talent.
How did this happen?
How did this suddenly happen?
Okay
His core should be very good
Yes
Impressive
It's possible
Talented
Yes, he learns quickly
Yes, really
When I saw him succeed
I actually felt it was expected
I thought he might learn quickly
But I didn't expect it to be so fast
Just find that feeling
I'm going to fall
If I'm really going to fall, let go
Let me go
We won't let you fall
We won't let go
Feel the change of the board in the water
Step down
And then let yourself
I can't step down
Double protection
Double
The biggest difficulty we encountered while surfing was
this sport is indeed a bit challenging for both of us
it is indeed a bit difficult
and actually, Wowo (Ren Jiabi) is a bit scared
but in the end, I found that she
might really find it hard to overcome
I think that kind of genuine
desire to protect someone
just makes you want to protect her
okay
perfect
Coach, don't move.
No way.
Alright
It's okay
No, at that moment I...
Really can't
It's fine
Let me tell you, I went rock climbing the day before yesterday
Because I have a severe fear of heights
Every time I climb to the top
They can just coolly
Let go directly
And jump down themselves
But that day, all of
I didn't dare to jump myself
I climbed up
And climbed back down myself
Actually, it's really silly, you know
Very tiring
Yes
So everyone definitely has
Their own fears they can't overcome
But I think it's like this
Actually, not everything
Needs to overcome this fear
He said this quite well
Definitely felt comforted
Even now
If you ask me to go rock climbing with you again
I still wouldn't dare to jump down
So it's okay
So actually, if today was rock climbing
I would come down first
Yes
So it's my problem
I think he is very patient
and he kept telling me
if you are really scared
we don't have to go down
we just need to experience this once today
that's already great
had a lot of fun
I think this is actually very important
a thing
I think the next activity
we really need to plan carefully
also looking forward to finding a
very suitable
shared activity
this shot is so beautiful
just soaking like this is nice
this might be a bit cold
be careful not to catch a cold
just playing with water is nice
playing with water and chatting is enough
yes
Have you had anything
you particularly want to do recently?
Rock climbing
Just at that moment
I suddenly wanted to go
I just wanted to see you a bit scared
Alright, sure
And you have long limbs
It would be easier to climb
Stop joking
Just now when I saw you sitting here
Your knees were over your shoulders
I didn't dare to sit straight
Do you know if I sit straight
where my knees would be?
My hands are also small, just like
My hands are small too, look
Yes
Little hands grab treasures
Can catch anything
Actually, everyone hopes for mutual effort
Yes
Actually, although at that time
I didn't know what you were thinking
But when I entered the room
While I was waiting
I thought if it was you knocking
The first thing I would say when opening the door would be
The person I was waiting for is you
I really feel like crying
Just a little bit
So I will still be more
firm in my
choice of people
This is blatant favoritism
But today I am really happy
I think today's sunshine and sun
are better than
better than the last two days
I just feel
the best plot is happening to me
I said in an instant
Do you dare to write a name?
I think the most straightforward way is to write a person's name
Then you are too brave
Then take another look tonight
Will tonight be a bit like that?
A bit nervous
For a moment, the sunlight hit the water surface
Then there was a person here
The whole environment looked like
Suddenly I recalled
I haven't encountered such a moment for a long, long time
Such a moment
It felt like a dream within a dream
I felt very dazed today
This light
The sunlight and atmosphere were just perfect
The timing, location, and people were all in harmony
The evening light is the most perfect
And the real-life scenes
Are truly much better than idol dramas
Yes
Indeed
This isn't just a single light shining
Yes
At this moment, everyone is their light
Indeed
What do you want to eat tonight
Tonight
What do you want to eat
Although you're not picky
But you surely have something you want to eat
I want to eat what you want to eat
I want to eat
Yunnan cuisine
Okay, let's go change clothes
Even introverted people change when they fall in love
You sit inside
Okay, I'll sit inside
This place smells really good
We didn't choose the wrong place, right?
Yes, I feel we chose the right place
We chose correctly
Thank you
You should add more beef
You worked hard today
Today, the water made me feel happy
Let's eat, I'm starving
These past two days
Have you gotten used to it a bit?
Life is quite normal
Actually, yesterday I was especially
I especially wanted to ask some questions at night
About your experiences before entering the small house
Some experiences
What exactly happened during this time
This is actually what I am most
Curious about
Yes
If someone else triggered this mechanism
I wouldn't think at all
That this is part of the game
But I suddenly feel
As if I did something
Actually, I have always been
curious about him
maybe even a bit skeptical
and then today started
You know,
yesterday I was also very
I didn't understand your expression
why it was like that
when I opened the door
I was surprised
and then embarrassed
and then a bit hesitant
like I didn't know what to say
My expression?
Yes
No
You gave me a feeling like
why are you here
I felt like I had an appointment
I believe that no matter how old you are
you will encounter love or something
But
I actually feel
there is still a sense of unreality
I have seen other perspectives
Later, I received such a task card
Within these three days
I must have a girl choose me
Then I can continue to stay in the cabin
Such a rule
I got curious again
about what I did that day
when I was just
talking about this
I briefly recalled
actually, that day
I did nothing
Yes
It was very quiet
You were very quiet
What I know about you is that you were very quiet
And yes
So the first date after that
probably wasn't because of me
Maybe it was this
Yes
You just need to know
the most important thing is
choosing you and completing the task
are not related at all
Really
This is me
Always from
Yesterday
I wanted to say it since yesterday, right?
After everyone received my message
I just
Actually, I don't care much about others
Whether they understand this matter
I care more about your thoughts
His directness is very comfortable
Very sincere
Yes
Because I'm afraid to tell you this way
You might not believe it
Actually, if I say
To complete this task
I can complete it in many ways
And Ren Jiabi is my
Least certain part
But everyone can see from my first day
Until today
You can feel it in every moment
There, you saw no slippers, right?
That's really fate
Imperfection is perfection
I am protecting you
Double protection, double
Then take another look tonight
I am very determined
If I had to choose a hundred times
I would still make this choice
I will explain to everyone
this matter
because it is necessary to mention
but I will tell you more
what you hear is different from what they hear
This adds a lot of points
He doesn't talk much
but every word is spot on
The two of you need to get a little closer.
Help!
Swing dance.
This was chosen by Kaka (Zheng Weiying).
Is it Kaka (Zheng Weiying) and the others?
This is so much fun.
Look, it's just the two of them.
Let's change direction.
This is easy.
Twist your hips a bit.
Yes.
Brother Zhang (Zhang Chenxi) is dancing.
This is so funny.
So cute, such a contrast.
I have zero experience with this.
I originally thought it was just
She is the main character, jumping around
Then I might just play along
and take some photos of her.
This kind of process.
But later I found out
First, find the rhythm of the music.
Brother Zhang's hands and legs move independently.
So funny
My frequency is a bit
We both play the main roles
We need to complete everything
I get quite nervous
Very restrained
Very unnatural
Then I revert to my usual
Very tense state
Worried about not doing well
This is too difficult for him
Yes
Okay, let's try it
Five, six, seven, eight
One, two
Each goes their own way
Anyway, the left foot and right foot are amazing
Five, six, seven, eight
One, two
Five, six
Yes, very good, yes
I just took a look
Kaka (Zheng Weiying) has already learned it
We are focusing on Zhang Chenxi
Brother Zhang is talking about me
Anyway, I also went through it
But I don't know how I got through it
So funny
Try Zhang Chenxi
Okay
The focus is not on the steps
It's more about the hips
Find this position, brother
Find where the hips are
You know you have hips, right?
I know I have hips
Still able to find the hips
It's good enough if he can find his left and right legs
Yes
Turn front and back
Front, back, turn
Front, back
Turn, turn, turn
Why is it a bit cute?
Brother, I think you should turn your body less
Just turn the hips
Try again
Okay
Like this
Yes
Turn your hips
Actually, I can clearly feel
Chen (Zhang Chenxi) is a person
who cares a lot about others' opinions
Wait a moment
Actually, I am too
When I see him
I feel a bit
like seeing myself
He needs a lot of encouragement
Relax
Chen is very cute in front of her
Return to position
Two, go
Three, return to position
Four, go
Not bad
Is it okay?
The more you dance, the smoother it gets
Alright
This isn't difficult for you
What else?
Can you
turn like this in place
I
How do I turn
Not bad
Prepare
Turn
Ready
Very good
Really very good
Have you learned this before?
I used to dance Mongolian dance
Come
Do a Mongolian dance, do one
Mongolian dance
What
His jump is pretty good.
His jumping ability is pretty good.
So high.
How is it so high?
The track was right in an instant.
Right.
Do it like that
Very impressive
You have great jumping ability
Not bad
So you have learned it too
No
That was purely a performance
And then there are those kinds of moves
Like riding a horse
I know
Just like that
What did you see
Take a quick shot
What is he
Is this horse riding
Very cute
I think you are a dance prodigy
Dance prodigy
Really
Thank you
Okay
Let's take a look
Our next move
This move has a name
It's called close position
So the two people are closer
I stand to the left of Teacher Lucy
Let's stand properly first
Then Zhang Chenxi, raise your right hand
And place it on Kaka's waist
Around this area
Brother Zhang
Happy
Then Kaka (Zheng Weiying)
Extend our left hand
Then place it on the back of our teammate
Everyone is very shy
Okay
Then let's take a look
We need to hold this hand
This is how our hand should be
My finger points to the right
Yes
Very good
So it's
Front Back
One two three four five six seven
Very good
Come
Let's all lift our heads
Yes, lift your heads
Yes
When we dance, our heads are lifted
Just look forward
Yes
It's just a boy
When he touches my body
I still feel shy
I still blush
Blush
I can clearly feel my heartbeat
Okay, sure.
Very good.
Excellent.
You can practice for a while.
Practice for a while first.
Then we'll prepare for the dance.
Alright.
Let's try that.
I saw that ballroom dance before.
It's like this.
Just like this.
One, two, three.
Almost
Maybe I'm a bit far away
Let's try again
Okay
He's been secretly laughing
It seems he's really enjoying it
I'll turn first
Then I'll turn again
I'm dizzy
Ready, go
So romantic
Then, collect
Great
Give yourself some encouragement
Okay
All our dancers, come in
Our dance party begins
Come
Hello everyone
This really feels like a ball
It's a ball
Relax a bit
There's also a ball
Ball
Find your dance partner and dance
Dance freely
I spun around in place
This is so much fun
It can still spin
Spin again
Keep spinning
So happy
Quite happy
Starting from breakfast today
To that date
I feel he prepared everything carefully
You thought of me
You are thoughtful towards me
I think it's very good
Good
I kept eating
You eat
It was all made for you
So considerate
When I was asked to choose again yesterday
I still chose this
Following my heart's choice
Okay, I heard that inner voice.
I heard it.
Right?
Got it.
Then
He might even show you
that he has experience in Mongolian dance from his childhood.
So cute.
Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi) deep inside
is a boy.
Relax.
This day, so far,
is the happiest day for me.
The atmosphere at that time
I really felt it was great.
Sometimes she
gives me that smile
which is quite infectious.
It unconsciously infects me.
It makes me happy too.
Such a moment
will always be
a very unforgettable date in my heart.
This is really good.
Good choice
Yes, good choice
This project (good choice)
How is it?
Zhang Chenxi's state is completely different.
A big change.
I've never seen him smile so happily.
He smiled so much that wrinkles appeared.
He smiled for such a long time.
He is just in front of others.
Actually, he has a big brother feeling.
Yes.
But in front of Kaka (Zheng Weiying),
he acts like a
big boy.
Yes, that kind of feeling.
This is the power of love.
Yes.
Actually, in Chen Ge (Zhang Chenxi),
as a guy,
I learned a lot.
A guy.
Don't talk about the person you fancy.
How many years older are you than him?
Don't be ashamed to show weakness.
Most men would want to say,
I want to lead my other half.
I want to do something for her.
Let her know that I am also great.
But actually today I saw,
when Zhang Ge (Zhang Chenxi) performed like this,
I instead felt,
he is adding points in Kaka's (Zheng Weiying) heart.
And also,
Hou Chengjie and our Wowo (Ren Jiabi's)
group's date
That group was also very good
You know, when I watched this
I cleared up a lot in the last episode
some blockages in my heart
Your blockage from the last episode
So, you mean
Mr. Luo, are you also watching the show?
It's like this
Take out your notebook and jot this down
Look, Hou Chengjie has a point
I also learned this
It means you're not having fun
This is what I prepared
The girl is afraid of water
Did you notice it?
Change it as soon as you notice it
Such a plan
It's okay, we won't try it then
We'll stand here and soak our feet in the water
That's pretty good
And there's one more thing
You must observe the other person immediately
Observe the other person's needs
Both of you might feel a bit awkward
At that time
It's not the time to show off
It's the time to focus on the other person
I just suddenly had a feeling
I think male viewers
should take a small notebook and jot this down
I wrote down a lot
I really think this is quite good
You are already so happy
and still want to continue improving your skills
Live and learn
Don't be ashamed to tell everyone
My wife and I are completely
actually from two different worlds
I can only say she is more patient
I was actually influenced by her
for seven or eight years
For the first seven or eight years
I was quite stubborn
But she made me willing to engage
with new things
It's not about influencing you
I want you to feel me
Teacher Luo, did you write it down, Teacher Luo?
This is worth noting down too.
Brother Hu, you have it tough.
You are speaking on one side
while also managing the class.
Yes.
But I really liked what you just said.
She is infecting you, not just influencing you.
Yes.
His core
makes me comfortable because
he respects my wishes and thoughts.
Yes.
What about Zhu Zhu?
I feel
Wo Wo (Ren Jiabi) and Hou Chengjie
seem to have turned on each other's switches.
When Wo Wo (Ren Jiabi) is surfing,
it's like she becomes a different person.
Yes.
It's the first time seeing
her having so much fun with a boy.
Smiling so brightly.
Hou Chengjie too.
I think his emotional value
is very fulfilling.
So we say
all introversion is just talking to the wrong person.
If you also want to find someone
who is on the same frequency and understands you,
you can go on the Soul APP.
You can go on the Soul APP.
Meet interesting souls who understand you.
Go on the Soul APP.
I think
One thing I really admire about Hou Chengjie is
he didn't tell her right away
you know, someone chose me yesterday
but I didn't agree
yes
and he didn't say
if no one chooses me, I'll be eliminated
he didn't say these things
I thought he said it from the beginning
this really makes a good impression
yes, it adds points, I think
he speaks with a great sense of propriety
and including when Wowo (Ren Jiabi) said
she seems to have some anxiety about her body
she doesn't dare to sit up straight
he didn't continue the topic
he changed the topic for her
he kept praising her long limbs
so encouragement
is really a very positive thing
it's very important
I'll borrow what Hou Chengjie just said
don't force it
if it really doesn't work, let's not do it
I actually find this quite useful
but I really need encouragement
that kind of person
for example, like diving
I actually have a fear of deep water
And often he would say
when we go to the beach
I might
feel timid because of this
but on the other hand
from his perspective
he wants me to see
a more beautiful world
so he would encourage me by saying
you really
otherwise you might regret it
but if it were the old me
I probably wouldn't go
but I might
because of his encouragement
I actually went deep diving once
What kind of partner is encouraging?
You feel
their presence is like a small power bank
constantly recharging you
especially when
your energy is low
you feel their energy coming
this is an encouraging partner
if we meet such a partner
cherish them
at the same time, we ourselves
should also be a power bank
yes
a good intimate relationship
everyone is a power bank for each other
must be mutually appreciative and encouraging
right
actually, encouragement is
when the other person is relatively weak
that it has value and meaning
yes
He can still sing
He
has a good mindset
His mental state is very healthy
What are you looking at?
I've already put away the ones I've finished.
Put all these paintings away.
So cautious.
How many have you painted?
Finished one.
So I'm in a hurry.
Do you usually paint like this at home?
You haven't painted for years.
Yes.
How do you paint this?
You.
Why did you come to look?
You're painting in a public place.
There's a sign outside saying it's reserved for Xia Xia (Xia Mengting).
No, that's impossible.
I entered the study first.
Go play by yourself.
Just like this.
Eat
Teacher Luo
Didn't see
Later
I'll tell you when it's ready to eat
Okay
Report
Not sincere
The bad man is here
You can eat now
You're so annoying
Sorry
Forgot, didn't see
Eat
Coming
Not sincere, bad man
He knows too
Their way of getting along is quite good
Yes
Alright
Still a bit cute
Forget it
Yes
A little less angry
I felt his care for me
Thank you
He would come to find me or pour me water
He said he would make noodles that day
He actually did it
I still hope to get along with Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
in a more relaxed manner
Everyone can interact as friends
The atmosphere is not as awkward as I imagined
It's still okay
At this point in time
I probably need to adjust my mindset
Didn't go on a date today
Just stayed in the cabin
Kind of unsure what kind of day it was
Nothing special happened
It was very ordinary
A bit boring
So red, look
So red
So beautiful
Remember with your eyes
I feel like I can't capture it
This beautiful feeling
Yes
Take a picture with your phone
Feels faint
Saw it yesterday
Saw it today
Does it feel different?
What's different?
Quick, tell me
The people around are different
When watching the sunset
I feel that maybe yesterday was more beautiful
Great, there's a sunset
Maybe it's because
she was there yesterday
She
This pronoun is quite romantic
He won't cry, will he?
I shed tears.
There's wind.
Very cliché
This saying is very cliché
It's true
If I am moved
I would say
We can pretend
It's okay
Tears are the best cosmetic for men
Broken
It's just a feeling
Just quickly gloss over it
Really cried
But
Of course, I'm curious where Liang Tian and the others went
Which one is it?
We are going to a concert.
I really like that one.
I like that kind the most.
Glad you like it.
There was a time when I especially liked listening to classical music.
Actually, it was after watching a TV series.
"Nodame Cantabile"
Me too.
My introduction to classical music.
Brahms.
Yes, Brahms.
The second theme.
Yes, the second symphony.
When the bass drum comes in.
Yes.
"Nodame Cantabile"
What a coincidence.
Yes.
I started listening because of that.
Classical music.
I also started listening to classical music because of "Nodame Cantabile."
That's how I got into classical music.
Whenever I see Brahms on the program.
I always go.
I started liking Mozart because of that.
The music style I like recently.
Is city pop.
Vaporwave or city pop.
That 80s style.
Yes.
I will play that music while working.
It's low-fidelity city pop music.
Low-fidelity music.
Yes.
It sounds great.
Then my mood will be a bit happier.
Yes.
I think I
I like things that are quite niche.
Talking about music-related stuff.
He thinks the music he listens to
is a bit niche.
Very niche.
But I didn't expect
when talking with me today
we could connect on so many things.
New Year's Eve candlelight concert.
For ladies, there's a rose.
You can give it to you.
You give it to me.
Thank you.
I said a girl should take a rose.
She gave it to me.
Okay.
You gave it to me, right?
Of course.
Very special
Yes
So cool
This place is really nice
Great choice
I found a really good place
Really impressive
The atmosphere is really important
You sit there, I'll sit here
Okay
It's starting
So beautiful
So lovely
Really
Next
Wonderful music is about to present you with
an unparalleled audiovisual feast
I really like listening
to tuning
It's kind of like we are all in sync
Yes
We are all in sync
Everyone speaks so well
I think if I watch a few more episodes, I can write a song
Sure
You can
I can really write a song
These are all lyrics
I really like this word
I really love "Howl's Moving Castle"
I especially love "Howl's Moving Castle"
This is my favorite
It has a very vivid imagery
This is the place
I really like the violin
This three-beat rhythm
Look, three-beat rhythm
Actually, when I listen to this song
At first, I feel like it's an old person
holding a nearly extinguished
lantern walking
then as it speeds up, it becomes younger
that's the story this movie tells
Actually, I'm just like her
My favorite is
the one from "Howl's Moving Castle"
"Life's Merry-Go-Round"
In my vision
this song from the very beginning
is very slow
like an old lady
then later it changes to a
three-beat rhythm
it's a bit like two people dancing a waltz
becoming younger and younger
I think this is very visual
Couldn't help but clap
I had heard of two cellists before
They formed a band
2Cellos
They are really in sync
That's great
He can take that
A seemingly low-key instrument
And play it in many different ways
Creating a lot of excitement
And at his concert
He always breaks the bow
But I think the breaking process
The visual impact is also striking
And it looks great
Yes
Never thought about it
Our tastes are really quite similar
I was quite surprised
Before I could say it
She also said 2Cellos
We said it at the same time
It felt like we were really in sync
The atmosphere was perfect
I'm really looking forward to
Getting to know you
I think it's not just about talking about life
But also talking about things we like
We never thought about it
Never thought about it
Tonight was really surprising
It's a Hayao Miyazaki special
During the concert
We both really enjoy it
when we hear a certain piece of music
then we will communicate with each other
Share the feeling after hearing this music
That kind of imagery
It's like
Holding hands and heading towards
Running together across the vast grassland
That low frequency comes out
Like that strong wind constantly blowing
Wind
I think
Our music tastes are quite similar
And we can understand each other when we talk
Happy i n g
My mood feels like riding a jet
Love i n g
Happy i n g
Changed dusk and dawn
With you, my heart races uncontrollably
The whole date, I felt
very comfortable
and relaxed
I knew the person I was talking to
was very positive and kind
Should we take the medicine?
Not bad
Quite romantic
For Liang Tian
I am definitely very satisfied
It's a bit like
Seeing a reflection in the mirror
Looking forward to continuing to date her in the future
We can find more
Similarities between us
Getting ready to cook
Making beef noodles
You're really good at chopping green onions now
Seriously, stop talking about it
This is sadder than not getting a date
You'll make me
think of this every time I chop onions
Is this the memory
I will take from the small house?
Okay
It's still early
I need some time to cook
It feels like it will be done around six or seven
That's early
They won't be back by seven
We can make the beef noodles and leave them
I'm really curious where everyone went today
I'm curious too
Still curious
They'll be back soon
Today is my first time
making beef noodles in the small house
I still feel a bit nervous
The main reason is
I want her to taste my cooking
Beef noodles are quite difficult to make
In a few days, those beef noodles
come and try making them
You can try making them, okay
Looking forward to it
He is still very dedicated
Then you need to fry the meat again
to add some color
Mix all the sauces
After throwing everything in
The flavor hasn't come out yet
I wonder if
I messed up the whole pot
After tasting it, I realized
It actually needs a bit more soy sauce
Adding it makes it delicious
I think this time the beef noodles
are a bit sweeter than usual
A bit sweeter
Shouldn't it be sour?
You found out
Generously
It's not a big deal
It looks so delicious
So delicious
I think it's ready to eat
Okay
I noticed you have a strategy
Just make a small bowl like this first
This will make it look very appetizing
I didn't mean to, it's us
There's only such a small bowl
There's no bigger one
The soup is so delicious
This soup is so delicious
Thank you
Is this a compliment to you?
So tasty
Do you usually make this at home?
Do you stew it for yourself?
Make this?
This is a bit too troublesome
Yes
Delicious
Good appetite
This child really doesn't pretend
Really doesn't pretend
Still want to eat
Leave some for others
It's not made for you
I'll scoop more meat
Save two pieces for Liang Tian
I originally thought its beef would
be very tough
but it actually tastes quite tender
I'll have another bowl
Another bowl, please
That's enough, brother
That's enough, stop eating
It's over
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) is heartbroken
That's hilarious
Sometimes he's really awkward
He doesn't know why people make this noodle
I want the ingredients
Want the ingredients
You should strain the soup
Strain it, got it
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) thinks you two are good
Originally, when making this beef noodle
I hoped Liang Tian could eat it
Will you have dinner when you come back tonight?
Because he has to cook dinner tonight
I will make beef noodles
Can you save me a little bit?
It should be delicious
Eat more meat, okay?
You should eat more
A lot
Thank you
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) really can't say anything
Just save a bowl for Liang Tian
I really didn't expect to say
It's Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
And Brother Luo (Luo Junfan)
Would support so much
Support
Eat so much
Go add some more quickly
Just eat this much
I want to take some back for a midnight snack
Still want to take some back
Don't be overly sure at this time
It's really delicious
Hurry and stop it
When I went to get the last bowl
I found there was only one piece of meat left
Only some red and white radishes were left
And maybe one or two pieces of mushrooms
They both finished eating
Liang Tian hasn't eaten yet
You say
Could Brother Luo (Luo Junfan) be a strategy
Absolutely not
Impossible
I think he's just mentally collapsed
And now he's just living here
Delicious
It's really tasty
I've eaten three bowls
So full
Very supportive
Thank you, everyone
It's really delicious
Really tasty
Do you want to watch a movie?
How about watching a movie?
Sure.
I'll get some fruit.
We can eat while watching.
I'm Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting).
I don't want to watch a movie here.
Exactly.
I'll hurry and stew the beef.
Who is this delivery person?
Is it Hou Chengjie?
He looks just like him.
Hello everyone.
You all seem to be living comfortably.
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting)
The blanket was lifted and then covered again.
No.
Do you want to come and sit with me?
It's okay, I'll go out for a bit.
Let's go.
Xiao Hou
Let's go out and have fun today
I noticed your face looks quite dry
So I bought you some men's facial cleanser from Watsons
and moisturizing lotion
For me? Thank you
Surfing today was really fun
But my face got a bit dry on the way back
My skin condition is a bit poor
Then try this set to take care of yourself
The facial cleanser has strong oil control
The lotion is light and very moisturizing
Many people are using it
Okay
I'll try it tonight
To moisturize
Then hurry up and try it
Guys should also pay attention to skincare
You can order more on Watsons' app when you run out
It can be delivered in 30 minutes
So convenient
It's available both online and offline
Then I'll buy skincare products from Watsons in the future
Fell asleep
The meat is gone, and the heart is "dead"
I want to know how you are today
They had fun
I didn't go down, I stayed by the shore
So you all changed into those clothes
He wore it without any pressure
I felt very sneaky
Then when I went out holding the board
Just like that
And then I came out like that
You could see they were having a lot of fun
Actually
And every time
Totally awkward
Yes, totally awkward
Was it like this today
I didn't dare, you know
It's just the clothes
But you know, during dinner
He sat next to me
Right?
No, not really
A little, you know
Very funny
Because in the restaurant actually
When I started to take off my coat
Because I knew this outfit needed
Needed to be handled like this
And he was sitting there, I felt awkward
I understand
Because I've worn this kind of clothes too
A conversation between girls
I just slowly turned around like this
You're here
Do you want to eat something?
I've already eaten
I'm looking for my water cup
Here
Really
Liang Tian is back
I haven't washed this yet.
You're awake.
Where did you go?
Went to a concert.
Concert.
What? Whose concert?
It didn't have a name.
It was one of those candlelight ones.
They played Joe Hisaishi's songs.
Talked a lot about music.
Joe Hisaishi.
Liang Tian must be happy.
Because Liang Tian and I both like Hayao Miyazaki.
Yes.
I was so mad I ate a plate of fruit.
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting)
Only when it's just the two of them
He becomes particularly outgoing
Hello
Are you feeling better today?
I heard you're still a bit dizzy.
She was completely out of it this morning.
I saw her this morning.
I'm feeling a bit better now.
But not much better, it still hurts.
I didn't notice this morning.
I thought you weren't fully awake.
No
I immediately changed into my pajamas.
Yes, I immediately changed into my pajamas.
I took a picture of you sleeping
Hello everyone
He fell asleep, Hu Yunting
Yes, he fell asleep
So funny
Fell asleep
So cute
What did you do at home today?
Today we had breakfast after waking up
Played volleyball here after breakfast
Almost broke everything here
Then went to watch the sunset
With Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) and Lao Luo (Luo Junfan)
Watched another sunset
Went to watch the sunset again
But there was no sun today
Yesterday was prettier
Not as pretty as yesterday
Then made beef noodles
The beef was all eaten
But the soup is still there
All eaten
There's still a piece of meat left
So pitiful
Can do it again
Will do it again
Alright
Then
Go watch a movie
Watch a movie
Then I accidentally fell asleep
Not bad
He didn't explain either
Nor did he say
He didn't say that someone else had finished it
Yes
His personality is probably one that doesn't explain much
So anxious
But if you don't tell her, how will she know?
Yeah
So close, yet not a single word
I didn't get to eat the beef noodles made by Hu Yunting.
It's still very regrettable
But he said he would do it for me later
I'm really looking forward to this.
It's as if we have this kind of agreement between us.
It's all because of that guy who ate three bowls.
Seriously.
Who is it?
Eats too much.
Even packed an extra portion.
To take home for a late-night snack.
Pack it up.
Message from Soul has arrived.
It's here.
Sent it.
Alright, started sending.
I posted my moment today
Brother Luo (Luo Junfan) and Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
on the balcony over there
watching the sunset
If Liang Tian sees it
then she will know what we did today
Even without a date
but I feel like today I
my whole state
adjusted very well
I still have expectations for love now
What I wrote in my moment is
the happiest day
experienced things I had never experienced before
overcame some of my psychological barriers
I posted two pictures
I think they are pretty good photos
She looks really good in them
Come on
Come on, please start
Look at people who have a clear goal
They don't even think about it
Today,
my date with Zheng Weiying
will probably stay in my memory forever.
And all of today's memories
are because of her involvement.
A rare smile
And we met again
All due to various coincidences
Coming together
Finally making it happen
And I find it quite amazing
Brother Zhang (Zhang Chenxi)
Here
How should I put it?
I've always said I stick to my principles.
Whoever I spent the most time with today,
I'll definitely post about that person.
As my moment of the day.
He deserves to be my moment of the day.
I think Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi) will definitely post about me.
My timidity is acting up.
I think Su Yonghao will definitely post about
Tiantian (Liang Tian).
So I don't think there's much to see.
Xiao Jie (Hou Chengjie) will definitely post about
Wowo (Ren Jiabi).
Watching anything today feels like watching loneliness.
I'll just watch something I've never seen before.
Actually, my feelings are very complicated.
I really admire Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi).
I think Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi) is also great.
But maybe Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi) for me,
his maximum likability,
can only reach eighty.
He might not reach one hundred percent.
Directly to the point of being able to fall in love.
I can see that.
So today I will be more clear that
I seem to like Su Yonghao.
I was clearly quite happy.
I think I will definitely find a
more suitable opportunity
to express my feelings.
She still cares about Teacher Su.
Oh my.
Whose post will she look at?
Mainly, I'm also quite curious
about his thoughts after last night's conversation
and today's series of interactions.
What will he think?
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) still hasn't moved on
and hasn't let go.
This moment is for myself
and also for Xia Xia (Xia Mengting).
What I posted today says
that the sunset actually represents
the arrival of a new day.
This actually represents my current
state of mind.
So beautiful.
It feels like a wilderness.
The things that happened a few days ago
end here.
From now on, I feel that in the cabin
I will start a new chapter.
To pursue what I truly need.
I also hope she can
with a fresh mindset
become a better version of herself
to welcome each new day.
Teacher Luo (Luo Junfan) took a solo path
Started on his own
Embarked on a solo journey in the world
Don't anyone interfere with me
I think Teacher Luo (Luo Junfan) in
His ability to express in life and love
Is much worse than in his career
Yes, it is
The moment I saw it, it was still Liang Tian's
Although we talked yesterday
We are interacting as friends
But I still hope
Her day goes relatively well
And actually, what I'm more worried about
Is probably her health
My entire left side
The area where the tonsils and nasopharynx meet
Is swollen
Wait a moment, I'll get you something
Even if it's just out of concern between friends
What I really care about is her health
Liang Tian
Tonight's rhythm
is already in the best state
then let time prove it
later I will definitely talk to her
about other different things
these things will become a piece of the puzzle
finally let the puzzle give me the answer
She knows he will look at her
This time, Liang Tian didn't send it to me.
Of course, I feel a bit disappointed.
But I also find it very understandable
Liang Tian's moment was probably sent to Su Yonghao
I guess it was a form of gratitude
It's just a date with Su Yonghao
This is very normal
I just can't let go
Let me do it
She should be looking at Su Yonghao
If I were in her position
I would also be looking at Su Yonghao
Who is she looking at?
Here she comes.
Su Yonghao is like the sun.
Very passionate, warm, and comfortable.
I'll help you carry it.
I'll help you move it.
You rest now, no need to come down yet.
Take a good rest.
Who knows how to use the washing machine?
I do.
Not surprising, right?
Not surprising.
Hello.
Hu Yunting feels like the moon to me.
A bit mysterious.
It stirs up thoughts.
Leads you to see and think.
Are you very tired?
Let's see what Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) does.
She might be more curious.
What did Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) do at home all day today?
Xiao Hu's (Hu Yunting's)
Because I think both the sun and the moon are pretty good.
But today I figured out the sun.
Next, I need to figure out the moon.
Last time I went on a date with Hu Yunting.
It was in the clouds on a cloudy day.
I parted the clouds a bit.
And saw the moon.
But this cloud didn't drift away.
I just can't see clearly.
He is hiding in the clouds.
Now I need to figure out
the moon behind the clouds that night.
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) is that moon.
Yes.
What's wrong?
The partner I was talking about is back.
It seems there's a turn of events.
A twist in the road.
Yes.
I'll go see.
What expression
He said it today
He said I should just write the name directly
You asked me yesterday
if I dared to write the name in an instant
but I knew it was definitely impossible
then take a look tonight
That's awesome
This is so romantic
Everyone laughed awkwardly
We made a joke
about the daily copy
and how hard it is to choose the pictures
I said the simplest way
is to send out the name of the person you like
send out the name of the person you like
it would be much clearer
So I confidently
sent out her name
So determined
At this moment, we exchanged a glance
She was thrilled
I just wrote a short essay
Writing a short essay
Short essay
It's because I'm afraid I'll be nervous
when I talk to everyone
so I might not be able to say this well
So I wrote it down today
What is Teacher Su (Su Yonghao) doing?
Why are you also gossiping?
I've already gossiped once, and now I'm doing it again
Actually, we discussed it during the day
I know that he
has a three-day survival rule in the small house
He said he would come back
and he couldn't wait
to explain everything to everyone
the whole story
He's quite a meticulous person
I guess everyone
already knows I have a task
and everyone
should be able to guess my task
After entering the small house
I actually only have three days
If within three days
I interact with all the girls
during the re-selection session last night
if no girl chooses me
I will have to leave the small house
At that time, I received this task
I actually wasn't particularly confident
I really wasn't particularly confident
Because I'm not good at expressing myself
I'm also a very slow-to-warm-up person
They added a time limit for me
And it was very quick
So for me
It might be an impossible task
Last night
I thought about having a meal with everyone
Because
I thought it might be my last meal in the cabin
The last meal
Actually, when I entered the cabin
I didn't even unpack my luggage
Until yesterday
Because I thought
It would be more convenient when I leave
That's all I have to say to everyone.
But I just
really want to say something to one person in particular.
Why are you looking at me?
Yesterday's choice
was not a part of my task completion
Especially after today
I feel I particularly don't regret it
and it was a very firm choice
He was really straightforward
Very firm
And it was in front of everyone
In the past two days, I took out "The Truman Show"
and watched it again
The director said this
The Truman Show is fake
but Truman is not
His world has no script
Perhaps it's not perfect
But it's genuinely real
It's a person's real life
So
I just need to explain to one person
That's enough
Just one person
And explain to one person in front of everyone
Yes, I won't say who it is
Yes
As long as that person understands
That's great
It's really a positive example
Really good
I always had a thought before
In the world of emotions
You need to be honest
You need to be open
Hello
I see from your expression that you have an appointment.
I'm here.
Waiting for you.
Has anyone ever asked you this question?
For example, do you believe in love at first sight?
You actually don't believe in it much.
I believe.
You believe, right?
But it seems it has never happened to me.
Then it's good that you believe.
You just need to know.
The most important thing is.
Choosing you.
Has nothing to do with completing the task.
I care more about your thoughts.
I only see one path I want to run.
And there's only one track.
I am willing to keep running on it.
Got goosebumps
They are like a drama couple
Romantic
A man's romance
Is Wowo (Ren Jiabi) crying?
No wonder he didn't interact with us much before
He was worried he might leave
Yes
Because I could see
He has been in that state for several days
A very tense state
Yes
He seemed burdened every day
So he relaxed
It's not that
We created this relaxed atmosphere for him
It's enough
Because the more relaxed he is, he might
Did Guo Guo (Ren Jiabi) cry from being moved?
Definitely, feeling very emotional inside.
Such complex emotions
It's hard not to shed tears
Because I always thought
I am someone who doesn't easily lose control
Actually, even now
I don't think
I would lose control
But today, indeed
I was deeply moved
When this really happened to me
It suddenly made me feel
Is this real?
I have a feeling of disbelief
I didn't expect it would affect her heart
and cause such a
I don't know if the word "impact" is appropriate
but what I really hope is
not because of this matter
and the impact it brought her
but rather
she feels that I am more important
He is really straightforward and persistent
I'm here
What kind of scene is this?
Just now it was from you
After finishing the whole monologue
Then I said I just ran away
But today, later on
I felt like I couldn't hold it together
That was very happy
Finally said what I wanted to say to everyone
Because actually, you know yesterday there were some
Not very harmonious voices in there
Some people might think I'm hesitating
Or not being firm
Actually, there were some doubts
But actually, I think
This doesn't affect me much
Because if we continue to interact
Because we still have to
Stay in the small room for such a long time
I will use my own feelings
To judge this matter
Sometimes I feel that people
Might say some insincere words
Or say some words that hide their true feelings
Or conceal some real things
So I think sometimes
your long-term interaction
and the process of feeling
might be more important
We are very similar
The similarity lies in
whether we would test
if the other person can take this step
But I didn't feel
you were testing
You always gave me a feeling of bravery
You have a kind of
unhesitatingly locking yourself in
You know, others give me the feeling
that they want to understand more
worried about being directly confined
But you are the opposite
I want to confine now
Then I am much happier than them
Whether I stay here for 21 days
or 210 days
If it's just to complete a task
or interact with someone
I am forced to interact with
Then I think I wouldn't be so open
I wouldn't be true to my feelings
But today, I am just behind
If you feel like you can't hold it together,
I just think that what you said
You said that thing
The world of Truman isn't real
But Truman is real
Then I just, I think
Then I just ran away
His words really hit me deep inside
I don't know how he knew
I might care about this point
Anyway, it hit me
In that place inside
It really hit
I'll ask you one question
If this question has an answer
I think nothing else matters
Would you be willing to
Take a step forward
Then the rest doesn't matter.
I feel very happy
I am just now
The question I just asked you
I just want to confirm your feelings one last time
It's me
But do you know
I might have been very subtle before
But actually, I think today for me
It has become very clear
I think everyone here can see it
Yes, everyone can see it
I also want to tell them
Stop guessing blindly
It's
It's Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
Yes, but
He seems to be very clear about it.
I won't always maintain
a very cautious and conservative attitude.
That is to say,
if a person is sincere at this moment,
I will also respond with sincerity.
From now on, when I post moments,
I will post names every day.
I will keep posting until the last day.
That's fine.
Then I'll think about it tomorrow.
Tomorrow, my moment
You can move freely.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
Good night.
Goodbye, good night.
Look, they just announced that we are going to date.
It's locked in.
Making breakfast.
Yes, she has work tomorrow morning.
Prepare something for her.
I'll make pancakes.
And a soft-boiled egg.
Openly and honestly,
be good to her.
She won't forget my name is Jeffrey, right?
Every day is just about romance
What do you think
about Hou Ge's (Hou Chengjie) actions
I think he's great
and he spoke very well
"The Truman Show"
Truman is real
but the world of Truman is fake
It fits this scenario perfectly
Yes
Hou Chengjie can always accurately
grasp and understand what Wo Wo (Ren Jiabi) is thinking
that hesitant answer
Actually, between the two of them
there has always been a barrier
In my opinion, that barrier is called rules
Until that barrier is broken
Wo Wo (Ren Jiabi) will doubt
if you are with me because of those rules
and want to stay with me
Even if Wo Wo (Ren Jiabi) doesn't think that way
I think Xiao Jie (Hou Chengjie) also wants to do this
to tell her and everyone
I just have one
firm choice
Yes
And I think there's a detail
that's particularly mature
When he expressed those words
he never publicly mentioned
the person's name
He chose to partially inform
and partially leave it unspoken between us
There is only one girl
who can clearly understand
who I am actually speaking to
but I didn't mention her name
Indeed, if he mentions Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
then everyone will start to make a fuss
and the girl will feel something inside
Yes
Yes, he might be thinking this way
That kind of subtle hint hits the hardest
Yes
Yes, actually the most important thing he did
the most correct gesture is
that all of us in love
need to learn
Actually, he is not saying
how I can win this girl
but first
I need to understand my own feelings
Now I am very determined
to express my feelings
You see, Xiao Jie (Hou Chengjie) never said
I am just trying to please you
Yes
I just want you to know
what I am thinking
I fell in love with you at first sight
I want you to know this
but I am not demanding
that you also fall in love with me at first sight
You see, this is very important
not to let yourself become
a mystery in the other person's eyes
It really made the other person feel comfortable
and respected
Yes
There is another person's condition
Actually, Luo Junfan
I don't know if he is carefree
or what
I saw his condition the next day
I actually found it a bit funny
How can he act like
nothing happened at all
First, let me tell everyone
the following words
are not to defend Teacher Luo
Since the last episode
everyone said it seemed like
they felt a bit blocked inside
Actually, the most blocked person should be me
because my filter shattered
But it was the first time I saw
him facing the opposite sex
facing love
I felt a bit flustered
even a bit absurd
He may not gain love
but he can gain growth
He can gain a lot of beef noodles
Three bowls
I admire his appetite
Really
Actually, this Gu Nian is quite obvious
You will find
When he is dealing with friendships
He is especially warm
Yes, a particularly good person
And he is also particularly cute
But he doesn't know how to handle intimate relationships
Yes
This is a lesson he needs to learn
This is something he must learn
I actually quite like
What Liang Tian just said
She described two boys
One is like the sun
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) is like the moon
If everyone based on your personalities
Would you choose someone like the sun
Or choose someone like the moon
Being with moon-type people
I feel quite tired
Like Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting)
He clearly does a lot of things
But he doesn't say anything
There will be many misunderstandings
I think Liang Tian is fine
She is very outgoing
Very lively and cheerful
Yes
She can handle it
She can handle moon-type people
Right
I am very determined
I hope he is a sun-type
Because the sun has a
very important characteristic
It is a star
It rotates on its own, it doesn't orbit other things
I am another star
We are attracted by universal gravitation
It can always shine on you
Yes
This is a very cute metaphor
But I think
It can actually express
At this moment, Liang Tian
After interacting with two people
Her feeling
Because when she just interacted with the sun (type)
We all saw that the atmosphere was very good
Suppose you put yourself in
If you were the person in that atmosphere
You would feel the romance of that environment
And then feel
That the person in front of you is cuter
I think the setting follows the people.
It can provide some support.
Actually, people can influence the environment.
The environment is a bonus.
But people are the primary factor.
The zeros added afterward only count.
In relationships,
I am quite reserved.
My wife used to perform in light music concerts.
She performed there for a long time.
But whenever I was in Beijing,
when I wasn't working,
I would always pick her up and take her home.
The road home,
she saw it as a date.
I probably didn't pay much attention to it.
She said,
I think what you've been doing,
might make me remember it for a long time.
That's quite romantic.
So you say the setting is useless,
but it does have its use.
But it is still based on
the feelings between two people.
And who the other person is.
You both gave
meaning to that road.
Yes.
Come on.
Let's quickly take a look.
at the next story.
Very pleasing to the eye
I never expected it to be a
new guy joining
His expression is really amazing
That upward curve of his lips
For his special date
A new female guest is coming
Regarding this matter
I still have high expectations
My heart is pounding
He has been waiting for this day
Truth or Dare
Draw two cards and try first
So
This is too exaggerated
Can you play this with me?
Sis Tian's terrified look, yes
Then I'll blindfold you
They want to lose, right?
Yes
Why don't we all check our phones
and make plans
with our friends?
There is always a voice in my mind
telling me
to be brave and give it a try
if the invitation fails
I won't have another chance
I hope I don't miss this opportunity
It feels very sneaky
secretly
this timing
really
I just want to say
I sent you the exact same characters
Your birthday is quite a coincidence
It's just one day away from Children's Day
Big friend
Although not a little friend
But a big friend
I think after talking about the pressure
Everyone feels better
I have a feeling that
Yesterday I talked about it
I feel much more relaxed
You should be firm
I am very firm
Especially after tonight, I am even more firm
Everyone
Old Hu, help me cover
Help me cover
Subtitles team, add a drumstick
So sweet
You understand me
So this is how others date
This is too happy
You must have felt great at that time
You should show it
Victory and defeat are common in war
Will support like this
I am really immature